pr9.net 2013-03-28

# PR9.NET Privacy Policy

**PR9.NET Privacy Policy**

Version 07/18/2004

* * *

PR9.NET is committed to protecting online user privacy. In order to ensure your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. 

  1. **What information does pr9.net collect?**

We use web log to collect information about your visiting, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on our site, and information about pages you visited. These information is automatically logged on our server in a "Web Log" file. This is a standard server function and most standard web sites utilize log files. The reason we use this information is to enhance our site and product offerings and maintain and secure our site. We retain this information for an indeterminate period of time. 

  2. **What is pr9.net practice regarding cookies?**

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to website. We use cookie to record press release publishers account name only. If you are a publisher, we provide a feature named "Remember account name on this computer", which uses cookie to remember your account name. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit your control panel. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information when, in which case we use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below. You may click here to remove the publisher account cookie on your computer. 

  3. **How does pr9.net use the information?**

If you are registered press release publisher of pr9.net, we will record the following information of you: account name, account password, contact name, contact E-mail, country. We will never sell or share these information to other companies or individuals. We also record (in optional) the following information about your company, which will be shown on your press release: E-mail address for press release contact, website URL, FAX, phone, company address and company introduction. 

  4. **Links to other sites**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site that collects information from you.

  5. **Privacy of children**

PR9.NET is not directed to children under the age of 13. If a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian may e-mail us, and we will remove the information from any promotional contact opportunities. 

  6. **How will I know if the privacy policy is changed**

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first within this page. If we are going to be using the information collected from users in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will send affected users written notice by email of the change. 

  7. **Give us your feedback**

We welcome your questions and comments about our Privacy Policy. Email us at info at pr9.net
